[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "A,G,C,E",
    "correctAnswer": 0,
    "notePicture": "trebleA3",
    "noteTone": "A3Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "E,A,F,C",
    "correctAnswer": 1,
    "notePicture": "trebleA4",
    "noteTone": "A4Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "G,B,C,A",
    "correctAnswer": 3,
    "notePicture": "trebleA5",
    "noteTone": "A5Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "F sharp,G sharp,C sharp,A sharp",
    "correctAnswer": 3,
    "notePicture": "trebleASharp3",
    "noteTone": "ASharpBFlat3Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "D sharp,G sharp,A sharp,F sharp",
    "correctAnswer": 2,
    "notePicture": "trebleASharp4",
    "noteTone": "ASharpBFlat4Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "A sharp,G sharp,F, sharp,C sharp",
    "correctAnswer": 0,
    "notePicture": "trebleASharp5",
    "noteTone": "ASharpBFlat5Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "A,C,B,D",
    "correctAnswer": 2,
    "notePicture": "trebleB3",
    "noteTone": "B3Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "D,B,A,G",
    "correctAnswer": 1,
    "notePicture": "trebleB4",
    "noteTone": "B4Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "F,C,B,D",
    "correctAnswer": 2,
    "notePicture": "trebleB5",
    "noteTone": "B5Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "C,A,E,G",
    "correctAnswer": 0,
    "notePicture": "trebleC4",
    "noteTone": "C4Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "G,A,E,C",
    "correctAnswer": 3,
    "notePicture": "trebleC5",
    "noteTone": "C5Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "A,C,E,G",
    "correctAnswer": 1,
    "notePicture": "trebleC6",
    "noteTone": "C6Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "D sharp,G sharp,C sharp,A sharp",
    "correctAnswer": 2,
    "notePicture": "trebleCSharp4",
    "noteTone": "CSharpDFlat4Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "A sharp,G sharp,F, sharp,C sharp",
    "correctAnswer": 3,
    "notePicture": "trebleCSharp5",
    "noteTone": "CSharpDFlat5Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "F sharp,G sharp,C sharp,D sharp",
    "correctAnswer": 2,
    "notePicture": "trebleCSharp6",
    "noteTone": "CSharpDFlat6Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "B,D,A,G",
    "correctAnswer": 1,
    "notePicture": "trebleD4",
    "noteTone": "D4Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "G,A,B,D",
    "correctAnswer": 3,
    "notePicture": "trebleD5",
    "noteTone": "D5Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "D,A,C,B",
    "correctAnswer": 0,
    "notePicture": "trebleD6",
    "noteTone": "D6Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "D sharp,F sharp,C sharp,A sharp",
    "correctAnswer": 0,
    "notePicture": "trebleDSharp4",
    "noteTone": "DSharpEFlat4Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "A sharp,C sharp,F sharp,D sharp",
    "correctAnswer": 3,
    "notePicture": "trebleDSharp5",
    "noteTone": "DSharpEFlat5Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "E,A,F,C",
    "correctAnswer": 0,
    "notePicture": "trebleE4",
    "noteTone": "E4Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "C,A,E,G",
    "correctAnswer": 2,
    "notePicture": "trebleE5",
    "noteTone": "E5Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "F,C,B,D",
    "correctAnswer": 0,
    "notePicture": "trebleF4",
    "noteTone": "F4Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "C,A,E,F",
    "correctAnswer": 3,
    "notePicture": "trebleF5",
    "noteTone": "F5Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "A sharp,G sharp,F, sharp,C sharp",
    "correctAnswer": 2,
    "notePicture": "trebleFSharp4",
    "noteTone": "FSharpEFlat4Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "F sharp,G sharp,C sharp,D sharp",
    "correctAnswer": 0,
    "notePicture": "trebleFSharp5",
    "noteTone": "FSharpEFlat5Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "C,A,E,G",
    "correctAnswer": 3,
    "notePicture": "trebleG3",
    "noteTone": "G3Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "G,A,E,C",
    "correctAnswer": 0,
    "notePicture": "trebleG4",
    "noteTone": "G4Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "D,B,A,G",
    "correctAnswer": 3,
    "notePicture": "trebleG5",
    "noteTone": "G5Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "F sharp,G sharp,C sharp,D sharp",
    "correctAnswer": 1,
    "notePicture": "trebleGSharp3",
    "noteTone": "GSharpAFlat3Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "G sharp,C, sharp,D sharp,A sharp",
    "correctAnswer": 0,
    "notePicture": "trebleGSharp4",
    "noteTone": "GSharpAFlat4Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 32,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "A sharp,C sharp,F sharp,G sharp",
    "correctAnswer": 3,
    "notePicture": "trebleGSharp5",
    "noteTone": "GSharpAFlat5Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 33,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "B flat,G flat,D flat,A flat",
    "correctAnswer": 3,
    "notePicture": "trebleAFlat3",
    "noteTone": "GSharpAFlat3Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 34,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "A flat,B flat,G flat,D flat",
    "correctAnswer": 0,
    "notePicture": "trebleAFlat4",
    "noteTone": "GSharpAFlat4Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 35,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "E flat,A flat,G flat,B flat",
    "correctAnswer": 1,
    "notePicture": "trebleAFlat5",
    "noteTone": "GSharpAFlat5Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 36,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "B flat,G flat,D flat,A flat",
    "correctAnswer": 0,
    "notePicture": "trebleBFlat3",
    "noteTone": "ASharpBFlat3Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 37,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "D flat,G flat,A flat,B flat",
    "correctAnswer": 3,
    "notePicture": "trebleBFlat4",
    "noteTone": "ASharpBFlat4Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 38,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "A flat,D flat,B flat,E flat",
    "correctAnswer": 2,
    "notePicture": "trebleBFlat5",
    "noteTone": "ASharpBFlat5Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 39,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "D flat,G flat,A flat,B flat",
    "correctAnswer": 0,
    "notePicture": "trebleDFlat4",
    "noteTone": "CSharpDFlat4Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 40,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "A flat,D flat,B flat,E flat",
    "correctAnswer": 1,
    "notePicture": "trebleDFlat5",
    "noteTone": "CSharpDFlat5Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 41,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "G flat,A flat,D flat,B flat",
    "correctAnswer": 2,
    "notePicture": "trebleDFlat6",
    "noteTone": "CSharpDFlat6Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 42,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "E flat,A flat,G flat,B flat",
    "correctAnswer": 0,
    "notePicture": "trebleEFlat4",
    "noteTone": "DSharpEFlat4Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 43,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "A flat,B flat,G flat,E flat",
    "correctAnswer": 3,
    "notePicture": "trebleEFlat5",
    "noteTone": "DSharpEFlat5Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 44,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "B flat,G flat,D flat,A flat",
    "correctAnswer": 1,
    "notePicture": "trebleGFlat4",
    "noteTone": "FSharpEFlat4Tone"
  },
  {
    "id": 45,
    "question": "What is this note?",
    "answers": "E flat,A flat,G flat,B flat",
    "correctAnswer": 2,
    "notePicture": "trebleGFlat5",
    "noteTone": "FSharpEFlat5Tone"
  }
]
